(this.webpackJsonpyopardy=this.webpackJsonpyopardy||[]).push([[0],{12:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"name":"JS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"When this is used, a variable can not be reassigned.<br />\u3053\u308c\u3092\u4f7f\u7528\u3059\u308b\u3068\u3001\u5909\u6570\u306e\u518d\u4ee3\u5165\u304c\u3067\u304d\u307e\u305b\u3093\u3002","answer":"const"},{"value":200,"question":"The context in which values are visible or can be referenced.<br />\u5909\u6570\u3084\u95a2\u6570\u306e\u5f15\u6570\u306a\u3069\u3092\u53c2\u7167\u3067\u304d\u308b\u7bc4\u56f2\u3092\u6c7a\u3081\u308b\u3082\u306e\u3002","answer":"scope"},{"value":300,"question":"The combination of a function with reference to its lexical environment.<br />\u95a2\u6570\u3068\u3001\u305d\u306e\u95a2\u6570\u304c\u5ba3\u8a00\u3055\u308c\u305f\u30ec\u30ad\u30b7\u30ab\u30eb\u74b0\u5883\uff08\u9759\u7684\u30b9\u30b3\u30fc\u30d7\uff09\u306e\u7d44\u307f\u5408\u308f\u305b\u3002","answer":"Closure"},{"value":400,"question":"The three most common ways to handle asynchronous operations in JavaScript.<br />JavaScript\u3067\u975e\u540c\u671f\u64cd\u4f5c\u3092\u884c\u3046\u6700\u3082\u4e00\u822c\u7684\u306a3\u3064\u306e\u65b9\u6cd5\u3002","answer":"Callbacks, Promises, async/await"},{"value":500,"question":"This is JavaScript\'s inheritance model.<br />JavaScript\u306e\u7d99\u627f\u30e2\u30c7\u30eb\u306e\u3053\u3068\u3002","answer":"The prototype chain"}]},{"name":"CS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The repetition of a sequence of computer instructions a specified number of times or until a condition is met.<br />\u30b3\u30f3\u30d4\u30e5\u30fc\u30bf\u3078\u306e\u547d\u4ee4\u30b7\u30fc\u30b1\u30f3\u30b9\u3092\u6307\u5b9a\u3055\u308c\u305f\u56de\u6570\u3060\u3051\u7e70\u308a\u8fd4\u3059\u3053\u3068\u3001\u307e\u305f\u306f\u6761\u4ef6\u304c\u6e80\u305f\u3055\u308c\u308b\u307e\u3067\u7e70\u308a\u8fd4\u3059\u3053\u3068\u3002","answer":"loop"},{"value":200,"question":"Time required for a function to execute based on its input size.<br />\u5165\u529b\u30b5\u30a4\u30ba\u306b\u57fa\u3065\u3044\u3066\u95a2\u6570\u304c\u5b9f\u884c\u3055\u308c\u308b\u306e\u306b\u5fc5\u8981\u306a\u6642\u9593\u3002","answer":"Big O notation"},{"value":300,"question":"Programming technique involving the use of a procedure, subroutine, function, or algorithm that calls itself one or more times until a specified condition is met.<br />\u30d7\u30ed\u30b7\u30fc\u30b8\u30e3\u3001\u30b5\u30d6\u30eb\u30fc\u30c1\u30f3\u3001\u95a2\u6570\u3001\u30a2\u30eb\u30b4\u30ea\u30ba\u30e0\u4f7f\u7528\u3057\u3066\u3001\u6307\u5b9a\u3055\u308c\u305f\u6761\u4ef6\u304c\u6e80\u305f\u3055\u308c\u308b\u307e\u3067\u30011\u56de\u307e\u305f\u306f\u8907\u6570\u56de\u81ea\u5206\u81ea\u8eab\u3092\u547c\u3073\u51fa\u3059\u30d7\u30ed\u30b0\u30e9\u30df\u30f3\u30b0\u6280\u8853\u3002","answer":"Recursion"},{"value":400,"question":"In this data structure, for any given node C, if P is a parent node of C, then the key (the value) of P is greater than or equal to the key of C.<br />\u4efb\u610f\u306e\u30ce\u30fc\u30c9\uff23\u306b\u3064\u3044\u3066\u3001\uff30\u304c\uff23\u306e\u89aa\u30ce\u30fc\u30c9\u306e\u5834\u5408\u3001\uff30\u306e\u30ad\u30fc\uff08\u5024\uff09\u306f\uff23\u306e\u30ad\u30fc\u4ee5\u4e0a\u3067\u3042\u308b\u3068\u3044\u3046\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u69cb\u9020\u3002","answer":"Heap"},{"value":500,"question":"A form of automatic memory management which reclaims memory occupied by objects that are no longer in use by the program.<br />\u5b9f\u884c\u4e2d\u306e\u30d7\u30ed\u30b0\u30e9\u30e0\u304c\u5360\u6709\u3057\u3066\u3044\u305f\u30e1\u30e2\u30ea\u9818\u57df\u306e\u3046\u3061\u3001\u4e0d\u8981\u306b\u306a\u3063\u305f\u3082\u306e\u3092\u81ea\u52d5\u7684\u306b\u89e3\u653e\u3057\u3001\u7a7a\u304d\u9818\u57df\u3068\u3057\u3066\u518d\u5229\u7528\u3067\u304d\u308b\u3088\u3046\u306b\u3059\u308b\u3082\u306e\u3002","answer":"Garbage collection"}]},{"name":"BACKEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The most popular Node framework, allowing us to write handlers for requests with different HTTP verbs at different URL paths.<br />\u6700\u3082\u4eba\u6c17\u306e\u3042\u308b Node \u30d5\u30ec\u30fc\u30e0\u30ef\u30fc\u30af\u3067\u3001\u30ea\u30af\u30a8\u30b9\u30c8\u306b\u5bfe\u3057\u3066\u3001\u7570\u306a\u308bURL\u30d1\u30b9\u3067\u3001HTTP verbs\u3068\u5171\u306b\u30cf\u30f3\u30c9\u30e9\u30fc\u3092\u66f8\u304f\u3053\u3068\u304c\u3067\u304d\u308b\u3002","answer":"Express"},{"value":200,"question":"Computer program or a device that provides functionality for other programs or devices, called \\"clients\\".<br />\u4ed6\u306e\u30d7\u30ed\u30b0\u30e9\u30e0\u3084\u30c7\u30d0\u30a4\u30b9\u306b\u6a5f\u80fd\u3092\u63d0\u4f9b\u3059\u308b\u30b3\u30f3\u30d4\u30e5\u30fc\u30bf\u30d7\u30ed\u30b0\u30e9\u30e0\u3084\u30c7\u30d0\u30a4\u30b9\u3067\u3001 \\"clients\\" \u3068\u547c\u3070\u308c\u308b\u3002","answer":"Server"},{"value":300,"question":"A small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user\'s computer by the user\'s web browser while the user is browsing.<br />Web \u30b5\u30a4\u30c8\u304c\u30e6\u30fc\u30b6\u30fc\u306e\u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b8\u30f3\u30b0\u4e2d\u306b Web \u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b6\u306b\u9001\u4fe1\u3059\u308b\u5c0f\u3055\u306a\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u3067\u3042\u308a\u3001Web \u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b6\u30fc\u306b\u4fdd\u5b58\u3055\u308c\u308b\u3002","answer":"Cookie"},{"value":400,"question":"A keyword in SQL that allows you to rename a column or table using an alias.<br />SQL\u3092\u4f7f\u3063\u3066\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u30d9\u30fc\u30b9\u304b\u3089\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u3092\u53d6\u5f97\u3059\u308b\u6642\u306b\u3001\u3053\u308c\u3092\u4f7f\u3046\u3068\u5217\u3084\u30c6\u30fc\u30d6\u30eb\u306b\u5225\u540d\u3092\u4ed8\u3051\u3066\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u3092\u53d6\u5f97\u308b\u3053\u3068\u304c\u3067\u304d\u308b\u3002","answer":"AS"},{"value":500,"question":"Refers to the management of incremental, reversible changes and version control for relational database schemas.<br />\u30ea\u30ec\u30fc\u30b7\u30e7\u30ca\u30eb\u30fb\u30c7\u30fc\u30bf\u30d9\u30fc\u30b9\u30fb\u30b9\u30ad\u30fc\u30de\u306b\u5bfe\u3057\u3066\u52a0\u3048\u305f\u5909\u66f4\u3092\u9806\u5e8f\u7acb\u3066\u3066\u30d0\u30fc\u30b8\u30e7\u30f3\u7ba1\u7406\u3059\u308b\u3053\u3068\u3002","answer":"Schema migration"}]},{"name":"FRONTEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The API to a webpage, allowing programs to read and manipulate the page content, structure, and styles.<br />Web \u30da\u30fc\u30b8\u306e\u5185\u5bb9\u3001\u69cb\u9020\u3001\u30b9\u30bf\u30a4\u30eb\u3092\u30d7\u30ed\u30b0\u30e9\u30e0\u3067\u8aad\u307f\u8fbc\u3093\u3067\u64cd\u4f5c\u3067\u304d\u308b\u3088\u3046\u306b\u3059\u308b\u305f\u3081\u306eAPI\u3002","answer":"DOM"},{"value":200,"question":"Describes all HTML elements, and includes content, padding, border and margin.<br />HTML\u5185\u306e\u3059\u3079\u3066\u306e\u8981\u7d20\u306b\u5bfe\u3059\u308b\u9818\u57df\u3092\u6307\u3057\u3001\u30b3\u30f3\u30c6\u30f3\u30c4\u3001\u30d1\u30c7\u30a3\u30f3\u30b0\u3001\u30dc\u30fc\u30c0\u30fc\u3001\u30de\u30fc\u30b8\u30f3\u306a\u3069\u3092\u542b\u3093\u3067\u3044\u308b\u3002","answer":"The CSS box model"},{"value":300,"question":"HTML5 convention via which HTML elements clearly describe their meaning to both the browser and the developer, as well as providing enhanced accessibility.<br />HTML5\u3067\u5c0e\u5165\u3055\u308c\u305f\u8a18\u8ff0\u65b9\u6cd5\u3067\u3001\u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b6\u3068\u958b\u767a\u8005\u306e\u4e21\u65b9\u306b\u5185\u5bb9\u3092\u660e\u78ba\u306b\u4f1d\u3048\u308b\u3060\u3051\u3067\u306a\u304f\u3001\u30a2\u30af\u30bb\u30b7\u30d3\u30ea\u30c6\u30a3\u3092\u5411\u4e0a\u3055\u305b\u308b\u3053\u3068\u304c\u3067\u304d\u308bHTML\u8981\u7d20\u3002","answer":"Semantic elements"},{"value":400,"question":"A React hook which serves the same purpose as componentDidMount, componentDidUpdate, and componentWillUnmount did in React classes, but unified into a single API.<br />React \u306e\u30af\u30e9\u30b9\u30b3\u30f3\u30dd\u30fc\u30cd\u30f3\u30c8\u306b\u304a\u3051\u308b componentDidMount\u3001componentDidUpdate\u3001componentWillUnmount\u3068\u540c\u3058\u76ee\u7684\u3092\u679c\u305f\u3059\u5358\u4e00\u306e API \u306b\u7d71\u4e00\u3055\u308c\u305f React \u30d5\u30c3\u30af\u3002","answer":"useEffect"},{"value":500,"question":"A JavaScript API for rendering interactive 2D and 3D graphics within any compatible web browser without the use of plug-ins.<br />\u4e92\u63db\u6027\u306e\u3042\u308b Web \u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b6\u3067\u3042\u308c\u3070\u3001\u30d7\u30e9\u30b0\u30a4\u30f3\u3092\u4f7f\u3046\u3053\u3068\u306a\u304f\u30d6\u30e9\u30a6\u30b6\u5185\u3067\u30a4\u30f3\u30bf\u30e9\u30af\u30c6\u30a3\u30d6\u306a 2D \u304a\u3088\u3073 3D \u30b0\u30e9\u30d5\u30a3\u30c3\u30af\u30b9\u3092\u30ec\u30f3\u30c0\u30ea\u30f3\u30b0\u3059\u308b\u3053\u3068\u304c\u3067\u304d\u308b JavaScript API\u3002","answer":"WebGL"}]},{"name":"CI/CD","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"It advocates adaptive planning, evolutionary development, early delivery, and continual improvement, and it encourages rapid and flexible response to change.<br />\u305d\u308c\u306f\u3001\u9069\u5fdc\u7684\u306a\u8a08\u753b\u3001\u9032\u5316\u7684\u306a\u958b\u767a\u3001\u65e9\u671f\u7d0d\u54c1\u3001\u7d99\u7d9a\u7684\u306a\u6539\u5584\u3092\u63d0\u5531\u3057\u3001\u5909\u5316\u3078\u306e\u8fc5\u901f\u304b\u3064\u67d4\u8edf\u306a\u5bfe\u5fdc\u3092\u5968\u52b1\u3057\u3066\u3044\u307e\u3059\u3002","answer":"Agile"},{"value":200,"question":"A software development practice where members of a team combine their work frequently.<br />\u958b\u767a\u8005\u304c\u983b\u7e41\u306b\u81ea\u5206\u306e\u30b3\u30fc\u30c9\u3092\u30de\u30fc\u30b8\u3059\u308b\u30bd\u30d5\u30c8\u30a6\u30a7\u30a2\u958b\u767a\u624b\u6cd5\u3002","answer":"Continuous Integration"},{"value":300,"question":"Design philosophy stating that rather than making users work around the product, the product should work around the user.<br />\u30d7\u30ed\u30c0\u30af\u30c8\u3092\u4e2d\u5fc3\u306b\u8003\u3048\u3066\u958b\u767a\u3092\u3059\u308b\u306e\u3067\u306f\u306a\u304f\u3001\u958b\u767a\u8005\u306f\u30e6\u30fc\u30b6\u30fc\u3092\u4e2d\u5fc3\u306b\u8003\u3048\u30d7\u30ed\u30c0\u30af\u30c8\u3092\u4f5c\u308b\u3079\u304d\u3067\u3042\u308b\u3068\u3044\u3046\u30c7\u30b6\u30a4\u30f3\u54f2\u5b66\u3002","answer":"User Centered Design"},{"value":400,"question":"An approach to building new businesses based on the belief that entrepreneurs must investigate, experiment, test and iterate as they develop products.<br />\u8d77\u696d\u5bb6\u304c\u88fd\u54c1\u3092\u958b\u767a\u3059\u308b\u969b\u306b\u3001\u77ed\u671f\u9593\u3067\u8abf\u67fb\u3001\u5b9f\u9a13\u3001\u30c6\u30b9\u30c8\u3092\u7e70\u308a\u8fd4\u3057\u884c\u3044\u3001\u958b\u6f14\u3092\u65bd\u3057\u306a\u304c\u3089\u65b0\u3057\u3044\u30d3\u30b8\u30cd\u30b9\u3092\u69cb\u7bc9\u3059\u308b\u30a2\u30d7\u30ed\u30fc\u30c1\u3002","answer":"Lean Startup"},{"value":500,"question":"Used to help a product manager (and others in the organization involved with the product\'s development) understand key traits, behaviors, goals, responsibilities, and needs of a specific type of user.<br />\u30d7\u30ed\u30c0\u30af\u30c8\u30de\u30cd\u30fc\u30b8\u30e3\u30fc(\u304a\u3088\u3073\u30d7\u30ed\u30c0\u30af\u30c8\u306e\u958b\u767a\u306b\u304b\u304b\u308f\u308b\u4eba\u3005)\u304c\u3001\u5546\u54c1\u3092\u5229\u7528\u3059\u308b\u30bf\u30fc\u30b2\u30c3\u30c8\u3068\u306a\u308b\u67b6\u7a7a\u306e\u4eba\u7269\u3092\u8a2d\u5b9a\u3057\u3001\u30e6\u30fc\u30b6\u30fc\u306e\u4e3b\u8981\u306a\u7279\u5fb4\u3001\u884c\u52d5\u3001\u76ee\u7684\u3001\u8cac\u4efb\u304a\u3088\u3073\u5fc5\u8981\u6027\u3092\u7406\u89e3\u3092\u6df1\u3081\u308b\u305f\u3081\u306b\u5c0e\u5165\u3055\u308c\u308b\u3002","answer":"Persona"}]}]')},15:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(34)},20:function(e,t,n){},34:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),s=n(10),o=n.n(s),i=(n(20),function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},"\ud83c\udf4d y o p a r d y")}),c=n(4),u=n(11),l=Object(u.a)((function(e,t){return{team:"t1",setTeam:function(t){return e({team:t})},selected:"",setSelected:function(t){e({selected:t})},answered:[],setAnswered:function(t){localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify(t)),e({answered:t})},score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},setScore:function(t){localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t));var n={score:t,lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()};e({scoreLastUpdated:n}),e({score:t})},scoreLastUpdated:{score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()},setScoreLastUpdated:function(t){return e({scoreLastUpdated:t})},reset:function(){var t={t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},n=[];localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t)),localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify(n)),e({answered:n}),e({score:t})}}})),m=Object(c.a)(l,1)[0],d=Object(a.memo)((function(e){var t=e.value,n=e.question,s=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),o=m((function(e){return e.answered})),i=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){s(n)}),[s,n]);return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:i,className:"question"},o.includes(n.question)?"\ud83e\udd51":t))})),p=n(3),b=n.n(p),f=function(e){var t=e.name,n=e.questions;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"column"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"column-header"},t),n.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement(d,{qid:e.id,key:b.a.generate(),value:e.value,question:e,answers:e.answers})})))},v=n(12),h=function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questions"},v.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement(f,{key:b.a.generate(),name:e.name,questions:e.questions})})))},w=Object(a.memo)((function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setTeam})),t=m((function(e){return e.team})),n=m((function(e){return e.score})),s=Object(a.useCallback)((function(t){e(t)}),[e]);return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"teams"},r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t1"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t1"},"TEAM 1 ","t1"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(n.t1<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},n.t1)),r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t2"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t2"},"TEAM 2 ","t2"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(n.t2<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},n.t2)),r.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){s(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t3"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t3"},"TEAM 3 ","t3"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",r.a.createElement("div",{className:"".concat(n.t3<0?"score-negative":"score-display")},n.t3)))})),g=n(14),E=n(1),q=n(5),S=n(6),y=n.n(S),N=function(e){var t=m((function(e){return e.selected})),n=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),s=m((function(e){return e.score})),o=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),i=m((function(e){return e.team})),u=Object(a.useState)(!1),l=Object(c.a)(u,2),d=l[0],p=l[1],b=m((function(e){return e.answered})),f=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),v=function(e){o(!0===e?Object(q.a)({},s,Object(E.a)({},i,s[i]+t.value)):Object(q.a)({},s,Object(E.a)({},i,s[i]-t.value/2))),n(null),p(!d)};return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal"},r.a.createElement(y.a,{bottom:!0},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-question"},t.question.split("<br />").map((function(e){return r.a.createElement("p",null,e)})))),d?r.a.createElement(y.a,{bottom:!0},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-answer"},t.answer.toUpperCase())):r.a.createElement("button",{className:"show-answer-button",onClick:function(){p(!d),f([].concat(Object(g.a)(b),[t.question]))}},"SHOW ANSWER"),d&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-buttons"},r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return v(!0)},className:"hell-yeah-button"},"HELL YEAH!"," ",r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u2705")),r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return v(!1)},className:"close-modal-button"},d?"NOPE":"CLOSE"," ",r.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u274c"))))},C=n(13),O=n.n(C);var T=function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),t=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),n=m((function(e){return e.reset})),s=m((function(e){return e.selected})),o=m((function(e){return e.scoreLastUpdated})),c=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){var t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("score"));t&&e(t)}),[e]),u=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){var e=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("answered"));e&&t(e)}),[t]);return Object(a.useEffect)((function(){c(),u()}),[c,u]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(i,null),r.a.createElement(h,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),s&&r.a.createElement(N,null),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-last-updated"},"SCORE LAST UPDATED:"," ",O()(o.lastUpdated).format("MMMM Do YYYY, h:mm:ss a").toUpperCase()),r.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){n()},className:"reset-score-button"},"RESET GAME"))};o.a.render(r.a.createElement(T,null),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.0a16ee36.chunk.js.map